<resources>
    <string name="EPFOnline11">✤ Ways to Check EPF Balance Online\10\10✤The EPFO has been introducing new methods for employees to check the EPF balance and is in the process of developing the existing platforms that can be used.\10\10✤ Online Portal\10\10✤ SMS Service\10\10✤ Missed Call</string>
    <string name="EPFOnline13">✤ EPFO introduced a new system to facilitate online submission of transfer claims by Members with an objective to make the transfer process transparent, efficient and comfortable for your employees.\10\10✤ You are urged to bring this facility to the notice of all your employees which is available on EPFOs Member portal.\10\10✤ A member has an option to submit his claim either through his present employer or the previous one.\10\10✤ You can see all such claim requests with ease, verify/correct member details, approve and submit the requests online through this portal.\10\10✤ For online submission of the claims, the Digital signature (Class II or above) of the authorized person is required.</string>
    <string name="EPFOnline14">✤ Visit the EPF Portal and click on ‘Our Services’ on the dashboard and click on For Employees.\10\10✤ Click on Member Passbook\10\10✤ The following details must be populated to log in to access the account.</string>
    <string name="EPFOnline19">✤ EPFO Recruitment 2019 Free Job alert for both Fresher and Experienced Candidates updated on March 12, 2019.\10\10✤ Get Direct Official Link for applying EPFO Recruitment 2019 along with current EPFO Recruitment official Notification 2019 here.\10\10✤ Find all recent EPFO Vacancy 2019 across India and check all latest EPFO 2019 job openings instantly here, Know upcoming EPFO Recruitment 2019 immediately here.</string>
    <string name="EPFOnline21">✤ View all Tender Notifications issued by Employees Provident Fund Organisation.\10\10✤ Search live eProcurement business opportunities available in EPFO Tenders section.\10\10✤Employees Provident Fund Organisation Tenders are further filtered by Bid Submission Date, Tender Value, Project Location &amp; Product Category.\10\10✤ Get email alert on Tenders from Employees Provident Fund Organisation - (EPFO).</string>
    <string name="EPFOnline23">✤ Step 1: Login to the Unified Portal of Employees’ Provident Fund (https://unifiedportal.epfindia.gov.in/) and click on For employees, followed by UAN Member e-Sewa.\10\10✤ Step 2: Enter UAN and password to log in to the portal.\10\10✤ Step 3: Click on Manage on the top panel and then on KYC\10\10✤ Step 4: On the next page, under Add KYC tab, provide your bank, PAN and Aadhaar, passport, driving license, election card and ration card details. Then click on submit. After submitting, you can find these details under Pending KYC tab. Once approved by the employer (which would generally take 15 days), it will be shown under Approved KYC tab.\10\10✤ Linking of your Aadhaar to EPF account will help in faster withdrawal and transfer process and for that, the present employer should have approved and verified the KYC including the employees Aadhaar details.</string>
    <string name="EPFService1">➺ An Employee Provident Fund is an initiative designed to offer social security benefits to employees of a particular organization, building stronger employee-employer bonds. In order to enjoy these benefits to the hilt, employers need to follow a set of rules and guidelines laid out, with registration forming the first step.\10\10✤ Employers need to provide the following details to successfully register themselves.\10\10➺ Name and address of company\10\10➺ Head office and branch details\10\10➺ Mention date of incorporation/registration of company\10\10➺ Fill up details of employees – total employee strength\10\10➺ Activity the business/enterprise is involved in – i.e. manufacturing, production, service, etc.\10\10➺ Legal details – This pertains to legal status of a company, i.e. whether it is a private firm/public company, partnership or society, etc.\10\10➺ Owner details, including designation and address of Directors and partners\10\10➺ Particulars related to wage component of employees, i.e. total wage disbursed during a month\10\10➺ Details of bank with whom company has banking relationship\10\10➺ PAN details\10\10➺ Basic details of employ\10\10✤ Documents required for EPF Registration Online :\10\10➺ Copy of partnership deed if the company is a registered partnership firm\10\10➺ A copy of the Certificate of incorporation for a Public or Private Limited Company. This should be issued by the Registrar of Companies\10\10➺ Societies should furnish a copy of their registration certificate\10\10➺ Public and Private Limited Companies need to submit a copy of memorandum and Articles of Association\10\10➺ Societies should furnish a copy of the rules and objects of the society\10\10➺ All legal documents which might be required under the Income Tax Act\10\10➺ PAN details of company\10\10➺ Partition deed\10\10➺ Proof of incorporation – first sales invoice/ license issued by competent authorities\10\10➺ Salary details of employees\10\10➺ Balance sheet details</string>
    <string name="EPFService2">➺ Upload KYC details in EPF UAN :\10To upload the KYC document on the EPF UAN, follow the steps mentioned below:\10\10✤ Visit the EPFOs member portal http://uanmembers.epfoservices.in/\10\10✤ Once the page is displayed on your screen, click on profile on the top bar. From the drop down list, click on upload KYC document.\10\10✤ Once you have clicked on that, select the KYC information you wish to update.\10\10✤ Next, you will have to upload a scanned self-attested copy of the KYC document. The document should be either in jpg, pdf or png format, and keep in mind that the maximum file size of your KYC document does not exceed 300 KB.\10\10✤ Once you have uploaded the document, the status of your KYC document will show as pending. Only once your employer has verified the document and approved of it, the status will show as approved by employer.\10\10✤ Once your employer has approved your document, you will receive an SMS confirming the same.\10\10✤ From then on, the verification process when you make a claim will be much faster and you can expect an approval in no time.\10\10✤ Process of embedding KYC details in EPF UAN :\10\10✤ Once your employer has verified and found the details matching and legitimate, he/she will digitally attest the document.\10\10✤ Once your document has been approved, authorities of the EPFO will then verify your approved document to see if there is any mismatch, discrepancies and so on.\10\10✤ If your documents hasnt been approved you can contact the EPFOs helpline - 1800 118 005 -or mail them at uanepf@epfindia.gov.in.\10\10✤ Once this is all done, if you raise a claim, the verification process will be done in no time and your personal KYC details will be embedded in the EPF UAN system.</string>
    <string name="EPFService3">✤ UMANG :\10\10➺ Unified Mobile Application for New-age Governance (UMANG) app was launched in November 2017 as a means of creating a common portal for all the facilities offered by the government. Additionally, other government developed programmes such as the Aadhaar and Digilocker are integrated with the app.\10\10➺ Umang offers over 180 government services to its users. One of these is the services offered by the EPFO. The EPF service on the UMANG app allows users to access information about their EPF account. This service is extended to both employers and employees. Though the EPFO tab on the UMANG app, employees can file claims for EPF withdrawal as well as track the status of their claims. Some of the requirements for using this facility is having your Aadhaar linked to the app, as well as an active UAN.\10\10➺ UMANG service has been made available on multiple channels like mobile application, web, IVR and SMS which can be accessed through smartphones, feature phones, tablets and desktops. UMANG has been created with a thought to add convenience to your lifestyle. UMANG will revolutionize the way how an Indian citizen avails government services today, because it leverages the current accelerated internet and smartphone penetration in our country.</string>
    <string name="EPFService4">➺ ECR/Returns and Payments :\10\10 ✤ Step 1: Login to EPFO portal using your ECR portal credentials: Once logged in, you can check the details of Establishment Name,Establishment ID, Exemption Status (PF, Pension, EDLI), Establishment Address and PF office.\10\10✤ Step 2: To upload ECR, go to Payments tab &gt;&gt; ECR [UPLOAD]\10\10✤ Step 3: On next screen, i.e. ECR File Upload, click on ECR Help File to view the ECR file format To upload the ECR, select the Wage Month and Salary Disbursal Date.\10\10✤ Step 4: Select your ECR text file to be uploaded. An ECR text file appears like the one below:\10\10✤ Step 5: Select the remaining fields like File Type (Select ECR), Contribution Rate % (Default value is 12%), add comment, and click on Upload Button:\10\10✤ Step 6: Once uploaded, the file will be validated by the portal against the pre-defined conditions. Once validation is successful, you can see the following screen with Validation Successful message: Click on Verify button to generate TRRN (Temporary Return Reference Number).\10\10✤ Step 7: Generate ECR summary sheet by clicking on Prepare Challan button\10\10✤ Step 8: On the next screen, you can adjust “Total EDLI Contributions (ER Share A/C 21)” (if required), enter Administration &amp; Inspection Charges for “Total EPF Charges (A/C 2)” &amp; “Total EDLI Charges (A/C 22).” Once done, click on Generate Challan Button.\10\10✤ Step 9: From the challan list page that follows, click on “Finalize” icon after reviewing the Total Amount, under Draft Challan List. You can also download Acknowledgment File and Receipt File under “In-Process Challan List”.\10\10✤ Step 10: The finalized ECR (Electronic Challan-cum-Receipt) will look similar to this:\10\10✤ Step 11: Once finalized, you can go ahead and make the payment. Click on “Pay” button to make the payment:\10\10✤ Step 12: Please select Payment Mode as “Online”, and select the bank from the list from which you wish to make the payment. Once selected, click on “Continue” and this will navigate you to payment gateway for completing the payment.</string>
    <string name="EPFService5">➺ We bring you steps that you must follow while applying for online EPF transfer.\10\10✤ Step 1: Go to the EPFO website, epfindia.com.\10\10✤ Step 2: The home page will show a section called online transfer claim portal. Click on it.\10\10✤ Step 3: Before logging in, check if you can apply online. If not, you will have to submit a physical copy of Form 13 to either your present or your previous employer.\10\10✤ Step 4: After checking the eligibility, log in and go to the claims section. There, click on request for transfer of funds.\10\10✤ Step 5: Form 13 will open. Fill your PF numbers with both previous and current employers and click on click here to get details. The name and address of the establishment, the PF account held by the EPFO and your name will appear on the screen.\10\10✤ Step 6: Your date of joining, date of leaving and father/spouses name also appear. This is to make sure that the money is transferred to the right account.\10\10✤ Step 7: You will be asked if you want to get the claim attested through your previous employer or your present employer\10\10✤ Step 8: You will have to type the characters shown in the text box and click on Get Pin. You will then have to agree to the declaration in the form by clicking on I Agree.\10\10✤ Step 9: Enter the PIN received on the registered mobile. The application is submitted.\10\10✤ Step 10: Tracking ID is generated.\10\10✤ Step 11: The form will be saved in the system. You have to take a printout of its PDF version, sign it and submit it to the employer within 15 days.\10\10✤ Step 12: Note down the contact details of people authorised to sign on the form. These are shown after the form is submitted.\10\10✤ Step 13: Present and previous employers will verify your details electronically.\10\10✤ Step 14: Once approval comes from both employers, funds are credited to the members account by the EPFO branch office.\10\10✤ Step 15: The employer plays an important role in this process by verifying the authenticity and signature of the employee.\10\10✤ The EPFO keeps you updated through SMSes. You can also track the application through the EPFO website.</string>
    <string name="EPFService6">➺ E-Passbook :\10\10✤ To avail the e-Passbook facility, you will have to compulsorily register on the EPFO official website. The following details will have to be filled in while registering:\10\10➺ Your mobile number\10\10➺ PAN number\10\10➺ Aadhar Card number\10\10➺ National Population Register number\10\10➺ Bank account number\10\10➺ Voter ID\10\10➺ Driving license\10\10➺ Passport number\10\10➺ Ration Card number\10\10➺ Your name as on the official documents\10\10➺ Email ID\10\10➺ You will get a captcha image, which you must type in the box provided and you will get the PIN.\10\10➺ The PIN will be received on your registered mobile number via SMS. After you submit the form, you will get a confirmation on your registered mobile and it completes the registration process. You can then login to the EPFO Member Portal and check your EPF status online.\10\10✤ The following is the process to generate your EPF e-Passbook:\10\10➺ Once you have logged in to the member portal, you will get a screen that you can alter your details and also download e-Passbook from this page.\10\10➺ When you select download, you will be asked to select the state and you will have to select the PF office of that state.\10\10➺ If you have no idea which is your PF office, you can find the details at http://epf-india.co.in/ .\10\10➺ You can then enter the EPF account number and your name that is the same as in your EPFO records.\10\10➺ Fill in the captcha details and avail the PIN number.\10\10➺ Enter the pin number that you receive on your registered mobile number via SMS.\10\10➺ Finally hit the button – Get Detail. You can then download the PDF e-Passbook.\10\10\10✤ Remember the following while downloading EPF e-Passbook:\10➺ Only one mobile number can be used for one registration.\10\10➺ You can however edit the mobile number later on.\10\10➺ You can see only one EPF account under one establishment.\10\10➺ You can transfer old EPF account to the new one.\10\10➺ You will not be able to see settled or inoperative accounts.\10\10➺ You can register using different ID proofs and mobile number to check the details of the different accounts.\10\10➺ Your EPF e-Passbook will contain the month and date wise transactions made in your account from the year in which the annual accounts were updated for the establishment.</string>
    <string name="EPFService7">➺ In order to link an establishment with your account you need to be registered at USSP, follow below steps:\10\10✤ To get started using the Shram Suvidha Portal right away, just type the following address into your web browser or click on the link below. https://shramsuvidha.gov.in\10\10✤ Search establishment LIN to link an establishment: Check establishment LIN through know your LIN option at portal main page menu.\10\10✤ If you find establishment LIN here, login to your Shram Suvidha account at portal home page. Below screen will be displayed, here enter login details:\10\101. user id\10\102. password\10\103. verification code Click on the submit button to view the landing page.\10\10✤ After login, you will see a menu at left hand side. Choose Link Establishment option from menu.\10\10✤ Now you will see link establishment form, fill out LIN number, previous representative contact details (registered mobile number and registered email id).\10\10✤ If you dont have mobile/email of previous representative, fill LIN number and choose generate authorization letter option. Meet your regional head with generated letter.</string>
    <string name="EPFService8">➺ Procedure for Generating Jeevan Pramaan / Digital Life Certificate :\10\10✤ Pre-Requisites for Digital Life Certificate Generation\10\10✤ The pensioner must have a Aadhaar number\10\10✤ The pensioner must have an existing mobile number\10\10✤ Registration of the Aadhaar number with Pension Disbursing Agency ( bank Post Office etc) should have been done already\10\10✤ Biometric device (list of supported devices is given on the JP portal)\10\10✤ PC with Windows 7.0 &amp; above Android Mobile/Tablet 4.0 &amp; above\10\10✤ Internet Connectivity</string>
    <string name="EPFService9">✤ What is a CoC?\10 Employees who are going on an assignment to a country with which India has an operational Social Security Agreement are exempted from contributing towards social security schemes in the other country (host country) if a CoC has been obtained from the EPFO.\10\10✤ Steps under the new online process :\10\10✤ EPFO has issued a user manual detailing the steps to be followed by the employee and the employer to apply for a CoC as per the new online process. Here is the step by step process for applying for a CoC. For employee:\10\10➺ 1. Visit the international workers portal on the EPFO website: https://iwu.epfindia.gov.in/iwu/ and select APPLICATION FOR COC.\10\10➺ 2. Mention Universal Account Number (UAN) and select appropriate member ID.\10\10➺ 3. Complete and submit the application. A reference number of the application will be generated upon submission and the pre-filled application will be available for download and print.\10\10➺ 4. Download and print the application. Sign the application and upload it along with a copy of ones passport.\10\10➺ To upload the signed application, visit the international workers portal and select UPLOAD SIGNED APPLICATION FOR COC. The employee can download the pre-filled application from here as well.\10\10✤ For employer:\10\10Once the employee has uploaded the signed application, the employer needs to follow these steps:\10➺ 1. Visit the international workers portal and login using the same login credential used for the Unified Portal (Employer).\10\10➺ 2. Select Certificate of Coverage from the tab Application.\10\10➺ 3. Select the appropriate Reference Number to get the signed application uploaded by the employee, verify all the details and approve / reject the application accordingly.\10\10➺ 4. Once the application is approved, download the application signed by the employee. To download, select Signed applications-Members under the tab Downloads.\10\10➺ 5. Take a print of the downloaded application and sign with date and stamp at the appropriate place.\10\10➺ 6. Upload the duly signed and stamped application. To upload, select Signed applications-Employer under the tab Upload.\10\10➺ Once the signed copy of the application is uploaded, the relevant PF office will process the application and generate the CoC accordingly.\10\10➺ Both employee and employer can track the status of the application from the international workers portal by selecting TRACK APPLICATION FOR COC and providing application reference number and date of birth of the employee.</string>
    <string name="InstantLoanGuide1">➺ Simply put, it is an unsecured loan taken by individuals from a bank or a non-banking financial company (NBFC) to meet their personal needs. It is provided on the basis of key criteria such as income level, credit and employment history, repayment capacity, etc.\10\10➺ Unlike a home or a car loan, a personal loan is not secured against any asset. As it is unsecured and the borrower does not put up collateral like gold or property to avail it, the lender, in case of a default, cannot auction.Simply put, it is an unsecured loan taken by individuals from a bank or a non-banking financial company (NBFC) to meet their personal needs.\10\10➺ It is provided on the basis of key criteria such as income level, credit and employment history, repayment capacity, etc. Unlike a home or a car loan, a personal loan is not secured against any asset.\10\10➺ As it is unsecured and the borrower does not put up collateral like gold or property to avail it, the lender, in case of a default, cannot auction.Simply put, it is an unsecured loan taken by individuals from a bank or a non-banking financial company (NBFC) to meet their personal needs.\10\10➺ It is provided on the basis of key criteria such as income level, credit and employment history, repayment capacity, etc. Unlike a home or a car loan, a personal loan is not secured against any asset. As it is unsecured and the borrower does not put up collateral like gold or property to avail it, the lender, in case of a default, cannot auction.\10\10➺ Simply put, it is an unsecured loan taken by individuals from a bank or a non-banking financial company (NBFC) to meet their personal needs. It is provided on the basis of key criteria such as income level, credit and employment history, repayment capacity, etc. Unlike a home or a car loan, a personal loan is not secured against any asset.\10\10➺ As it is unsecured and the borrower does not put up collateral like gold or property to avail it, the lender, in case of a default, cannot auction.</string>
    <string name="InstantLoanGuide2">➺ It can be used for any personal financial need and the bank will not monitor its use.\10\10➺ It can be utilised for renovating your home, marriage-related expenses, a family vacation, your childs education, purchasing latest electronic gadgets or home appliances, meeting unexpected medical expenses or any other emergencies.\10\10➺ Personal loans are also useful when it comes to investing in business, fixing your car, down payment of new house, etc.</string>
    <string name="InstantLoanGuide3">➺ Although it varies from bank to bank, the general criteria include your age, occupation, income, capacity to repay the loan and place of residence. To avail of a personal loan, you must have a regular income source, whether you are a salaried individual, self-employed business person or a professional.\10\10➺ An individuals eligibility is also affected by the company he is employed with, his credit history, etc.</string>
    <string name="InstantLoanGuide4">➺ It usually depends on your income and varies based on whether you are salaried or self–employed. Usually, the banks restrict the loan amount such that your EMI is not more than 40–50% of your monthly income.\10\10➺ Any existing loans that are being serviced by the applicant are also considered when calculating the personal loan amount.\10\10➺ For the self employed, the loan value is determined on the basis of the profit earned as per the most recent acknowledged profit/Loss statement, while taking into ac…</string>
    <string name="InstantLoanGuide5">➺ It is good to compare the offers of various banks before you settle on one. Some key factors to consider when deciding on a loan provider include interest rates, loan tenure, processing fees, etc.</string>
    <string name="InstantLoanGuide6">➺ Although the loan sanctioning criteria may differ from one bank to another, some key factors determining the maximum loan amount that can be sanctioned to you include your credit score, current income level as well as liabilities.\10\10➺ A high credit score (closer to 900) means you have serviced your previous loans and/or credit card dues properly, leading the lenders to feel that you are a safe borrower, leading to a higher loan amount being sanctioned. Your current income level and liabil ..</string>
    <string name="LoanType1">➺ If you need a loan quickly, a personal loan may be an option for you.\10\10➺ A personal loan is an unsecured loan and you get it quickly.\10\10➺ But yes, you can expect the interest rate of a personal loan to be higher than a secured loan. Let us know in detail about personal loans.\10\10➺ First of all, personal loan is available very quickly.9 Some banks even claim that they will give you a loan in a few minutes. Do not just go to claims. But yes, you can expect to get a loan soon.\10\10➺ Secondly, personal loan is unsecured loan. That is why you do not need to have some security.\10\10➺ This is one of the reasons for getting loan soon. Because less documents are required, that is why the loan is available sooner.</string>
    <string name="LoanType3">➺ To promote small enterprises in the country, the government has introduced several loan schemes. Apart from the Pradhan Mantri Mudra Yojana, there are many other schemes in which you can take small loans to big loans.\10\10➺ At this time, according to the schemes of the central and state government, you can take a loan of Rs 50,000 to Rs 1 lakh for your business.\10\10➺ Actually banks decide to give you a loan according to your business plan. If the bank feels that your business and profits from it will be so much that you will be able to repay the loan of the bank within the stipulated period after completing your expenses, only then the bank approves your loan.\10\10➺ What are the benefits of taking a business loan? Financial support for inward business needs of cash to meet financial needs for both short and long term.</string>
    <string name="LoanType4">➺ Everyone\'s dream is to have a branded car with them at home. A car not only makes your life comfortable, but also reduces many difficulties. Reaching the office while battling public transport or going out for weekends, everything becomes very easy.\10\10➺ Earlier, buying a car was a big thing for anyone, because it had to spend a lump sum, but now it is very easy due to the easy availability of a car loan.\10\10➺ Banks and non-banking finance companies offer car loans on easy monthly installments, which has made it very easy to buy cars. Due to this, your budget is not deteriorated and convenience is also available.</string>
    <string name="LoanType5">➺ Quality education is very important for a person\'s complete and successful life. For some people it may be a graduation from a top institute. At a time when the cost of studies is constantly increasing, the cost of studying in the top institutes of the country and abroad is quite high.\10\10➺ Keeping this in mind, parents invest in mutual funds, some fixed deposits and some resort to ULIPs. Even after all this, the amount may be less for your studies.\10\10➺ Education loan helps you a lot in such situations. This loan fills the gap between your need and the money available.\10\10➺ According to a study, the cost of studies is increasing at the rate of 15 percent annually. At this time, if the cost of studies is Rs 2.5 lakh, then after 15 years, it will cost Rs 20 lakh to do MBA.</string>
    <string name="LoanType6">➺ Sometimes we need money in emergency. In this case, gold kept at home can be quite useful. Companies like Manapuram Finance, Muthoot Finance, IIFL offer gold loans.\10\10➺ Some government and private sector banks also offer gold loans. You can take cash by pledging gold ornaments, coins etc. After paying this money, the pledged jewelery or gold is returned to the customer.\10\10➺ Interest has to be paid on the loan amount. Gold loan has lower interest rate than personal loan. Personal loan.. How much interest do you think?\10\10➺ Finance companies and bank interest rates are different for gold loans. These range from 1 percent to 15 percent. For example, ICICI Bank charges interest from 1% to 16.50% per annum on gold loans. Along with this, one percent charges processing fee.</string>
    <string name="app_name">Instant Loan Guide and EMI Calculator</string>
    <string name="balance_online">✤ Log in to the EPFO website and click on the Our Services tab. \10\10✤ Choose the For Employees option from the drop-down menu. \10\10✤On the login page, enter the username which is the UAN and password to log in. \10\10✤Once logged in, employees can access their EPF details. \10\10✤Click on the respective passbook to check your EPF balance with different employers.</string>
    <string name="cliam_link">https://www.epfindia.gov.in/site_en/Downloads.php?id=sm8_index</string>
    <string name="epf_online_title10_detail">✤ View all Tender Notifications issued by Employees Provident Fund Organisation. \10\10✤ Search live eProcurement business opportunities available in EPFO Tenders section. \10\10✤ Employees Provident Fund Organisation Tenders are further filtered by Bid Submission Date, Tender Value, Project Location and Product Category. \10\10✤Get email alert on Tenders from Employees Provident Fund Organisation - (EPFO).</string>
    <string name="epf_online_title11_detail">✤ Step 1: Login to the Unified Portal of Employees’ Provident Fund (https://unifiedportal.epfindia.gov.in/) and click on For employees, followed by UAN Member e-Sewa. \10\10✤ Step 2: Enter UAN and password to log in to the portal. \10\10✤ Step 3: Click on Manage on the top panel and then on KYC \10\10✤ Step 4: On the next page, under Add KYC tab, provide your bank, PAN and Aadhaar, passport, driving license, election card and ration card details. Then click on submit. After submitting, you can find these details under Pending KYC tab. Once approved by the employer (which would generally take 15 days), it will be shown under Approved KYC tab. \10\10✤ Linking of your Aadhaar to EPF account will help in faster withdrawal and transfer process and for that, the present employer should have approved and verified the KYC including the employees Aadhaar details.</string>
    <string name="epf_online_title12_detail">✤ EPF 24×7 Customer Care Number and Toll Free Helpline- Employee Provident Fund \10\10✤ And Head Office Address List Are Blow Plz Click The Button.</string>
    <string name="epf_online_title1_detail">✤ Ways to Check EPF Balance Online \10\10✤The EPFO has been introducing new methods for employees to check the EPF balance and is in the process of developing the existing platforms that can be used. \10\10✤ Online Portal \10\10✤ SMS Service \10\10✤ Missed Call</string>
    <string name="epf_online_title2_detail">✤ Step 1: Go to the EPFO portal. Click on Our services&gt; For Employees \10\10✤ Step 2: Click on Know Your PF Status \10\10✤ Step 3: Enter your UAN and enter the captcha image \10\10✤ Step 4: Enter the following details ➺ Enter the state of your PF office ➺ Select your PF Office from the drop-down menu ➺ Enter your establishment code ➺ Enter your Provident Fund account number \10\10✤ Step 5: Click on the Submit button to check the status of your PF claim.</string>
    <string name="epf_online_title3_detail">✤ EPFO introduced a new system to facilitate online submission of transfer claims by Members with an objective to make the transfer process transparent, efficient and comfortable for your employees. \10\10✤ You are urged to bring this facility to the notice of all your employees which is available on EPFOs Member portal. \10\10✤ A member has an option to submit his claim either through his present employer or the previous one. \10\10✤ You can see all such claim requests with ease, verify/correct member details, approve and submit the requests online through this portal. \10\10✤ For online submission of the claims, the Digital signature (Class II or above) of the authorized person is required.</string>
    <string name="epf_online_title4_detail">✤ Visit the EPF Portal and click on ‘Our Services’ on the dashboard and click on For Employees. \10\10✤ Click on Member Passbook \10\10✤ The following details must be populated to log in to access the account.</string>
    <string name="epf_online_title5_detail">✤ Types of EPF Claim Forms \10\10✤ Form 19: This is to be filled in case of final settlement of PF account by a member. \10\10✤ Form 10C: This is to be filled for claiming Scheme Certificate/Withdrawal Benefit as per Employees’ Pension Scheme 95. \10\10✤ Form 10D: This is to be filled for pension claims. \10\10✤ Form 20: This is to be filled for claiming PF by legal heir/nominee on death of a member. \10\10✤ Form 5IF: This is to be filled for claiming assurance benefit as per Employees Deposit Linked Insurance 76 by legal heir/nominee of a member. \10\10✤ Form 31: For claiming advance/temporary withdrawal as per Employees Provident Scheme 52. \10\10✤ Form 13: For transferring PF/pension between different accounts. \10\10✤ Form 14: For financing a life insurance policy out of the PF account</string>
    <string name="epf_online_title6_detail">✤ Multiple job changes typically result in multiple Employee Provident Fund (EPF) accounts being opened, one with each employer. \10\10✤ With the introduction of the UAN (Universal Account Number), it is possible to consolidate multiple accounts into one single account for each EPFO member. \10\10✤ Retirement fund body EPFO offers a facility to its members that allows consolidation or merger of their multiple PF accounts with the current universal account number (UAN).</string>
    <string name="epf_online_title7_detail">✤ To avail the e-Passbook facility, you will have to compulsorily register on the EPFO official website. The following details will have to be filled in while registering: ➺ Your mobile number ➺ PAN number ➺ Aadhar Card number ➺ National Population Register number ➺ Bank account number ➺ Voter ID ➺ Driving license ➺ Passport number ➺ Ration Card number ➺ Your name as on the official documents ➺ Email ID ➺ You will get a captcha image, which you must type in the box provided and you will get the PIN. ➺ The PIN will be received on your registered mobile number via SMS. After you submit the form, you will get a confirmation on your registered mobile and it completes the registration process. \10\10✤ You can then login to the EPFO Member Portal and check your EPF status online. \10\10✤ The following is the process to generate your EPF e-Passbook: ➺ Once you have logged in to the member portal, you will get a screen that you can alter your details and also download e-Passbook from this page. ➺ When you select download, you will be asked to select the state and you will have to select the PF office of that state. ➺ If you have no idea which is your PF office, you can find the details at http://epf-india.co.in/ . ➺ You can then enter the EPF account number and your name that is the same as in your EPFO records. ➺ Fill in the captcha details and avail the PIN number. ➺ Enter the pin number that you receive on your registered mobile number via SMS. ➺ Finally hit the button – Get Detail. You can then download the PDF e-Passbook. \10\10✤ Remember the following while downloading EPF e-Passbook: ➺ Only one mobile number can be used for one registration. ➺ You can however edit the mobile number later on. ➺ You can see only one EPF account under one establishment. ➺ You can transfer old EPF account to the new one. ➺ You will not be able to see settled or inoperative accounts. ➺ You can register using different ID proofs and mobile number to check the details of the different accounts. ➺ Your EPF e-Passbook will contain the month and date wise transactions made in your account from the year in which the annual accounts were updated for the establishment.</string>
    <string name="epf_online_title8_detail">✤ Types of EPF Claim Forms \10\10✤ Form 19: This is to be filled in case of final settlement of PF account by a member. \10\10✤ Form 10C: This is to be filled for claiming Scheme Certificate/Withdrawal Benefit as per Employees Pension Scheme 95. \10\10✤ Form 10D: This is to be filled for pension claims. \10\10✤ Form 20: This is to be filled for claiming PF by legal heir/nominee on death of a member. \10\10✤ Form 5IF: This is to be filled for claiming assurance benefit as per Employees Deposit Linked Insurance 76 by legal heir/nominee of a member. \10\10\10✤ Form 31: For claiming advance/temporary withdrawal as per Employees Provident Scheme 52. \10\10✤ Form 13: For transferring PF/pension between different accounts. \10\10✤ Form 14: For financing a life insurance policy out of the PF account</string>
    <string name="epf_online_title9_detail">✤ EPFO Recruitment 2019 Free Job alert for both Fresher and Experienced Candidates updated on March 12, 2019. \10\10✤ Get Direct Official Link for applying EPFO Recruitment 2019 along with current EPFO Recruitment official Notification 2019 here. \10\10✤ Find all recent EPFO Vacancy 2019 across India and check all latest EPFO 2019 job openings instantly here, Know upcoming EPFO Recruitment 2019 immediately here.</string>
    <string name="link_Activate_UAN">https://passbook.epfindia.gov.in/MemberPassBook/Login.jsp</string>
    <string name="link_BalanceOnline">https://passbook.epfindia.gov.in/MemberPassBook/Login.jsp</string>
    <string name="link_Check_Your_EPF">https://epfindia.gov.in/site_en/</string>
    <string name="link_Download_Claim_Form">https://www.epfindia.gov.in/site_en/Downloads.php?id=sm8_index</string>
    <string name="link_Downloads">https://www.epfindia.gov.in/site_en/Downloads.php?id=sm8_index</string>
    <string name="link_E_Passbook">https://passbook.epfindia.gov.in/MemberPassBook/Login.jsp</string>
    <string name="link_FAQs">http://pfapp.mypfbalance.com/faq.html</string>
    <string name="link_Locate_Office">http://search.epfoservices.org:81/locate_office/office_location.php</string>
    <string name="link_Member_Passbook">https://passbook.epfindia.gov.in/MemberPassBook/Login.jsp</string>
    <string name="link_Multiple_PF_Accounts_of_an_Employee">https://passbook.epfindia.gov.in/MemberPassBook/Login.jsp</string>
    <string name="link_News">https://news.google.com/news/search/section/q/employee%20provident%20fund/employee%20provident%20fund?hl=en&amp;gl=US&amp;ned=us</string>
    <string name="link_Online_Transfer_Claims_Portal_OTCP">https://www.epfindia.gov.in/site_en/OTCP_ForEmployers.php</string>
    <string name="link_Pensioners">https://mis.epfindia.gov.in/PensionPaymentEnquiry/</string>
    <string name="link_RTI">https://www.epfindia.gov.in/site_en/RTI.php?id=sm12_index</string>
    <string name="link_Recruitments">https://www.epfindia.gov.in/site_en/Recruitments.php?id=sm9_index</string>
    <string name="link_TRRN_status">https://unifiedportal-epfo.epfindia.gov.in/publicPortal/no-auth/misReport/home/loadSearchTrrnHome</string>
    <string name="link_contact_US">https://www.epfindia.gov.in/site_en/Contact_us.php</string>
    <string name="linnk_Tenders">https://www.epfindia.gov.in/site_en/Tender_Auction.php?id=sm10_index</string>
    <string name="locate_office">✤ Visit the EPFO website and click on the “Locate an EPFO Office” option. \10\10✤ Alternatively, click on the link http://search.epfoservices.org:81/locate_office/office_location.php to find EPFO offices directly. \10\10✤ In case you want to know the EPF office having jurisdiction over an address, select the first option. \10\10✤ Now select your state or union territory from the drop down list and select the district where you want to locate the EPF office. \10\10✤ Results will be displayed containing the details of the regional office and the office under whose administrative control the office is operating. \10\10✤ In case you want to know the jurisdiction of an EPF office, then click on the second option and select the office from the drop down menu and click on the submit button. The result displayed contains the complete address of the office and e-mail address of concerned authorities. \10\10✤ Results are displayed on the screen mentioning the state, district, jurisdiction area and the jurisdiction status of the office.</string>
    <string name="news">✤ Epfo की ताज़ा ख़बर, ब्रेकिंग न्यूज़. \10\10✤ plz Clilck The Button.</string>


    <string name="app_id">ca-app-pub-3940256099942544~3347511713</string>
<!--    <string name="ads_native">/6499/example/native</string>-->
<!--    <string name="interstail">/6499/example/interstitial</string>-->
<!--    <string name="banner">sw</string>-->
</resources>